

#### INFO

**PROFESSION** 

Full Stack Developer

DATE OF BIRTH

29/Oct/1987

EMAIL

syyed.devcamp360@gmail.com

PHONE NUMBER

+1 204 520 0620

WEBSITE

https://ahsankazmi5.github.io/ahsandev/

**ADDRESS** 

Charlottesville, VA

#### EDUCATION

BACHELOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (2009 - 2013)

University of Virginia Charlottesville, VA

DIPLOMA IN ASSOCIATE ENGINEERING

Swedish Institute of Technology

# SYED AHSAN KAZMI

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER



## **PROFILE**

I started my career in the agency world where I was given an opportunity to work on some amazing private brands. With this experience in my back pocket, I was able to land the role of a Full Stack Developer at Iplex.

In my free time I enjoy spending time with friends and family. Daily I go for at least a one hour walk while listening to music on Soundcloud, this is where I get most of my creative ideas. I love fast Bikes and have a Ride2, one day I hope to own a BMW K1200S, in the meantime I'll keep working hard towards my dream.



### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Sep 2019 - Present

Full Stack Developer

Lab270 KY, US

July 2016 - Present

Wordpress developer

**IPlex** 

Aug 2015

Junior Php developer

e Coder

Nov 2014

Frontend developer

Plex

Mar 2014

Junoir Web developer (Php, Forntend)

**Agile Solutions** 



## **RECENT PROJECTS**

Autoplex Alberta https://www.autoplexalberta.ca/

Metal Buddies https://metalbuddies.com/

LIEBESTIPPS www.liebestipps.com

USA WILD SEA FOOD www.usawildseafoodapp.com

AVERAGE LOW www.averraglow.com

TRUCK TRANSPORT www.trucktransport.com

NTS MOVING www.ntsmoving.com

AUTO MOTIVE LEADS www.automotiveleads.com

PORSCHE www.porsche.dealerleads.com

COGNITOYS www.cognitoys.com

DCAS www.demo.dcas.biz



BACKEND/FRAMEWORKS	FRONTEND
PHP/Laravel	HTML5/CSS3/
Wordpress	Bootstrap
Shopify	Javascript/jQuery
	React.js
TOOLS/ARCHITECTURES	DATABASES
GitHub, Slack, Trello	MySQI
Jira, Asana	Mongo.DB
WOOCOMMERCE STORE	DESIGN
WP Woocommece	Adobe Photoshop
Shopify Store	Adobe Experience (XD)
Templating online builders	Adobe Illustrator